Your objective is to find The Dark Lord and defeat him.
To get him you should go through five floors of his lair - Castle Thalion.

Use "arrows" to move on rooms and "space" or "enter" buttons to interact with a room.
To go up to next floor you should find an Exit [X] and use it.

Going through the Castle you can meet enemies who will try to kill you.
Battles occur step by step: at first it's your turn, further it's enemy's turn and etc.
You should choose one of the hero's abilities (Use "arrows") to apply it (use "space" or "enter").

Every class of a hero and every enemy have own charactiristics:
	∙ HP (Hit Points: quantity of Damage what the hero can get before he will have died);
	∙ Dmg (minimal and maximal Damage);
	∙ Accuracy (probability of hitting on an enemy);
	∙ Crit (probability of making a Critical Damage);
	∙ Dodge (probability of Dodging from enemy's attack);
	∙ Defence (a percentage of Damage that will be blocked when enemy's attacking).
Hero's defence, dodge and critical chance can't be more than 50%.

Every ability has several modificators from the next ones:
	∙ Mod.Acc (increases or decreses base hero's accuracy);
	∙ Mod.Dmg (increases or decreses base hero's damage);
	∙ Mod.Crit (increases or decreses a chance of a ctitical hit);
	∙ Stun (a chance of Stunning. If you stun an enemy, he will miss his next turn);
	∙ Bleeding (a chance of Bleeding, damage by Bleeding and quantity of turns, during which Bleeding is affecting);
	∙ Poisoning (a chance of Poisoning, damage by Poison and quantity of turns, during which Poison is affecting).
Every enemy has a chance of a resistance to Bleeding and Poison. Try to understand who and what resistance has.

Going through the floors you can find gold, keys, chests [?] and special items, changing hero's characteristics.
There is a store [$] on an every floor, where you can buy health potions, keys and special items for gold.
